[music]
Today's going [music] to change my life.
What's for breakfast? Jesus Christ
spoken the [singing] bear one night at a
time
dropping from the sky. Guess it's time
to bake a [singing] pie. Making [music]
our own good luck. Now there's a penny
in the lake, but it's [singing] not what
[music] I thought.
It's just someone's wish they forgot.
[singing]
There's [music] a penny in the lake, but
it's [singing] not what I thought.
It's [music] just someone's [singing]
fish there.
[music]
Motor bike is running [singing] fine.
Whiskey in the summertime.
The bugs are writing books with their
eyes. Big old dancer cuts a rug. Stubs
her toe on a [singing] slug. It's your
classic slip and slide down. [music]
There's a penny [singing] in the lake,
but [music] it's not what I thought.
It's just someone's wish [music] they
forgot.
There's a [singing] penny in the lake,
but it's not what I thought.
It's just someone [music] fish there.
[music]
Peace in love to drive my car. Baby,
[music and singing]
you're my ringo star. Twisting the radio
dial
off too far. I scream at chain [music]
link fence. A travel by coincidence.
So you'll never see [music and singing]
me again.
There's a penny in the lake, but it's
not what I thought.
It's just [singing] someone's wish they
[music] forgot.
There's a penny [singing]
in the lake, but it's not what I
thought.
[music] It's just someone's [singing]
will say for God.
[music]
>> [music]
[cheering]
>> Thank you. [applause]
Thank you. Thank you so much for
clapping.
Thanks for standing here in the room
with us. Okay. Wow. So surreal to be
here.
We've been watching these uh Tiny Desk
concerts since back in the family
desktop computer days. So,
here we are. All right, guys. Ready?
Song's called What's Right with a
Question.
Heat. Heat.
Sam
running down the laundry line of
[singing] stars that won't collide.
Falling out [singing] of sight of you.
[music]
Falling out of sight of you.
You see the little things alive.
It won't hurt just right.
But now we're running out of gas in the
middle of the night.
And I think you know.
I think you know.
I think you know what's right this time.
Yeah, I think you [music] know what's
right this time.
Yeah, I think [singing and music] you
know what's right.
>> [music]
>> Will you look [singing] me in the eye
and promise that you stay with me till
the sand meets the sky?
[music] Like the telephone lines
that go forever.
They go forever.
They go.
And I think you know.
I think you know. [music] I think
[singing] you know what's right this
time.
[music] Yeah. I think you know what's
right this time. Oh, I think you [music]
know what's right this time.
Oh, I think you know what's [singing]
right.
Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat up
here. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> My subconscious is a [music and singing]
man.
He softly says to me, "I'll vanish when
[music] you need me [singing] to. I'll
hold you when you sleep."
And as I take his [music] hand,
I know just where I am. My sleeping
[music] eyes, they open wide, looking up
the stairs again. And it's just one of
those things, you know, I want to take
[music] control, but I lost it in a
dream where I could [music] have had it
all.
One
more.
Take it back. [singing and music] The
moon that shines is talking smack to me.
I feel it all. [singing] The beck and
call [music] the elevator tings in the
distant end [music and singing] as I
walk in washes over me and says, "Break
all your concentration.
Love your self."
And these thoughts of desperation
[music]
embrace
help. [music]
My subconscious is a man.
He softly says to me, [music]
"I'll [singing] be there when you need
me, too. I'll hold you when you sleep."
Every last [music] impression I had
before I turned away
was feeling so damn comfortable even
[singing and music] though I couldn't
stay.
[applause]
[cheering]
Thank you.
Okay, [music]
we got one more for you. I forgot to
introduce ourselves. As El said, we're
called Rap Boys. We're from Chicago,
Illinois.
It's a true honor to be here. Thanks to
NPR for holding it down with public
independent media in the year 2026.
[applause]
All right,
this one's for the chillers out there.
Let's do it.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Ooh.
[music]
Ah.
>> [music]
>> How I ever know you quite like [music] I
was [singing] told to make sure you love
each other nice now. [music and singing]
Oh, I was hypnotized, caught up in the
[music] northern light,
driving around in circles,
singing, "Hey,
now [music and singing]
what was that sound?"
hide in a match just for the freak it
out.
Then on the other side, I [music] saw 50
[singing] yellow lines,
pushing up [music]
against the window.
And with one almighty lightning strike,
the great lake rose [singing and music]
up behind said, "Baby, you best turn
around." [music and singing]
So [music] I went back. I went back to
the shore [music]
to follow your path away forever more.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music] Wow.
[music]
Heat.
>> [music]
>> Hey,
hey, hey.
Heat. Heat.
[music]
Hey.
Heat. Heat. N.
[music]
Heat. Heat. [music]
Heat. Heat. Heat. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat. Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat.
[music]
That's [singing] all. That's
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat. [music]
>> Crushing the blades. Great train. Make
the wind [music]
blow away.
Kick it back. Don't leave me out. If
that mocking bird don't sing, [singing]
why you do the twist again?
Does that [music and singing]
freak you out?
>> If she's twisted up too tight, [singing]
let the dawn cut through the [music]
night.
>> Kick it back. Don't leave me out. If
that day slowly break, make your way
down to the lake. [music]
Does that
freak you out?
Does that [music and singing] black
freaking out?
>> [music]
>> Thanks [cheering] so much. [applause]
Thanks for having us.
Thanks to Josh for running. [applause]
[cheering]
>> [applause]
[applause]
[cheering]
>> A quick update before you go. We're
doing another Tiny Desk giveaway. Enter
by September 12th, 2026, and you and a
friend could win a free trip to DC to
see a Tiny Desk concert live [music] in
person. You even get to choose which
upcoming show you want to see, and it's
completely free to enter. Just go to
npr.org/tinyes
giveaway. Entering is completely free,
but you can get more entries by snagging
some limited edition Tiny merch or by
making a special donation to the NPR
network. Learn more and enter today at
npr.org/tinyeskaway. [music]